[Music]
let me guess I'm in a talent show come
on oh no you're the judge of the talent
show to be more precise it's a
children's house you like Sal doesn't
know is that the kids are in on it they
know that Sal's a plant judge the
audience though no idea she kept dancing
this kids alright - lets go yell I
ordered chicken wings an hour ago
I ordered chicken wings an hour ago it
was really beautiful to watch thanks so
much for that great performance make
sure the girl knows that you order
chicken wings an hour ago too
when you give your feedback I was having
a hard time concentrating on it only
because I ordered my lie what had
chicken wings an hour ago I called that
out while you were dancing it's hard
enough to sit through a kid's talent
show it's hard enough it's fun it's hard
enough to you guys know this it's hard
enough to sit through a kid's talent
show despite the fact that you know you
got to eat you know I oughta cheat
anyways forget the chicken wings that
was great under your tables a bag of
potato chips open it up and make it as
loud as possible while you're opening it
[Music]
great very nice that was good not great
that was that was good
not
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
so you jump so your town this you jump
see then you just jump them
you ever see your kangaroo have you ever
seen like a kangaroo they jump they jump
they don't get awards for it do they
they don't get awards for it though do
they
the audience is shooting you daggers
thank you
[Applause]
last one last one buddy last one damn
that landing that's a good form
[Music]
sounds do you want to get up and do some
karate moves
Sal show me move watch this
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
I could take in a fight
I can take you in a fight we know that
[Music]
[Applause]